http://www.amerfirst.org/privacy-policy

Your security is important to us
Please be cautious this holiday season. We will NEVER ask you for sensitive personal identification information via email, phone, or social media unless you contact us. If you suspect fraud or spam, please notify us right away at 800-290-1112.
Learn More
Don't show again
Privacy Policy
Home Disclaimers Privacy Policy
Why does American First Credit Union gather your personal information?Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.What does American First Credit Union do with your personal information?The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include:Social Security numberName, address, and email addressCard numbersLocation informationAccount balances and payment historyWe may also gather additional information, such as the type of device and browser you are using, the IP address of your device, information about your device’s operating system, and additional information associated with your device. We may also gather information collected through cookies and other technologies, as described further below.How does American First Credit Union use your personal information?All financial companies need to share customers' personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their customers' personal information; the reasons American First Credit Union chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.Guidelines for collecting and storage of member information.As a general rule, American First does not automatically collect personal information. The submission of personal information is initiated by the website visitor. We limit the amount and type of information new collect and retain that which is required to establish and manage your account, understand your needs and provide services, offer new products and services, and comply with legal and regulatory requirements. It is our policy that personal information, such as your name, postal address, email address, and telephone number, is private and confidential. Accordingly, the personal information you provide is stored in a secure location and is accessible only by designated staff, and is used only for the purpose for which you provide the information.Third-Party DisclosureWe do not disclose or sell personal information about you or our former members to non-affiliated third parties, except as permitted or required by law or regulation or as specified above. We may disclose all of the information we collect to companies with whom we have a financial services agreement to offer financial products and services to you.Reasons we can share your personal informationReasons we can share your personal informationDoes American First Credit Union share?Can you limit this sharing?For our everyday business purposes -such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureausYesNoFor our marketing purposes -to offer our products and services to youYesYes For joint marketing with other financial companiesYesYes For our affiliates' everyday business purposes -information about your transactions and experiencesNoWe don’t shareFor our affiliates' everyday business purposes -information about your creditworthinessNoWe don’t shareFor our affiliates to market to youNoWe don’t shareFor non-affiliates to market to youYesYesWhat we doHow does American First Credit Union protect my personal information?To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.How does American First Credit Union collect my personal information?We collect your personal information, for example, when youOpen an account or Deposit MoneyPay your bills or Apply for a loanUse your credit or debit cardWhy can't I limit all sharing?Federal law gives you the right to limit only:sharing for affiliates' everyday business purposes - information about your creditworthinessaffiliates from using your information to market to yousharing for non-affiliates to market to youState laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing.DefinitionsAffiliatesCompanies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and non-financial companies.American First Credit Union has no affiliatesNon-affiliatesCompanies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and non-financial companies.Non-affiliates we share include investment, insurance, and other financial services companyJoint MarketingA formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you.Our joint marketing partners include investment, insurance, and other financial services companiesCalifornia Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA)California residents have the consumer right to require a business to disclose the who, what and why of its information-sharing practices, to limit or require the deletion of personal information in some instances, and to be free from discrimination for exercising those rights; andBusinesses are required to disclose and provide information about its information collection and sharing practices in response to a verified consumer request available on its websiteConsumers have theRight to request disclosure of the categories and specific pieces of personal information the business collects or sellsRight to request deletion of any personal information collected (subject to exceptions)Right to opt-out if the information is sold to third partiesRight to nondiscrimination if the consumer exercises their rightsCCPA Form CCPA NoticeTo limit our sharingCall toll-free 800-290-1112 to speak with a Member Service RepresentativeFill out the opt-out form below and mail or bring it to your nearest American First branch; or fax it to American First Credit Union at 562.237.5111Email us at contactus@amerfirst.orgIf you are a new member, we can begin sharing your information 45 days from the date we sent this notice. When you are no longer our member, we continue to share your information as described in this notice, however, you can contact us at any time to limit our sharing.Download Opt-Out FormQuestions?Call us at 800-290-1112
Welcome
Close
Open an Account
Bank with Us
Make a Loan Payment
Products & Services
Home Loans
Vehicle Loans
Aa
We use cookies to provide you with the best experience on our website. By clicking okay, you agree to our use of cookies in accordance with our cookies policy.
Okay
